I mean, you could say, "Thank you."
I did just buy you a car.
Lock, I admit that it's odd that
Rajesh didn't write to you himself,
(Amy:)but if you get to know him, you'll
see he's just a sweet, regular guy.
As a counterpoint, here he ls,
uninvited and visibly sweaty.
(Raj:)-Hello, Emily.
-Hello.
(Raj:)Amy told me you were concerned
that I might be too passive and shy.
(Raj:)Let me ask you something.
(Raj:)Would a passive guy barge in here
to look you in the eye and say,
"Hey, dew-kissed flower, what's up?"
(Emily:)No, but a weird guy
with no boundaries might.
(Raj:)Okay, that's a separate issue.
(Raj:)Let's put a pin in that
and just focus on the passive thing.
(Emily:)I'm leaving.
(Amy:)Are we still going to go to
that Chaucer reading Friday?
(Emily:)You know, I think
I'm just gonna go by myself.
(Raj:)Not my best first date.